<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tarot</string>
    <string name="info">info button</string>
    <string name="main_info">Tarot works by tapping into the subconscious mind through symbolism and intuition. A deck of cards is shuffled and laid out in a spread, each card representing archetypal energies or aspects of life. The reader interprets these cards, drawing on their intuition and knowledge of symbolism to provide insights into the past, present, and future. It\'s not about predicting a fixed outcome, but rather guiding reflection and understanding to navigate life\'s complexities.</string>
    <string name="one_card_info">In a one-card draw, focus on a specific question or situation. Shuffle the deck with intent, then draw a single card. This card represents the essence of your inquiry or the energy surrounding your situation. Reflect on its imagery, symbolism, and intuition to glean insights. It offers a snapshot or advice for the present moment, guiding your thoughts or actions with clarity and intuition.</string>
    <string name="three_card_info">In a three-card draw, shuffle the deck and focus on your query. Draw three cards and lay them out in a sequence, often past-present-future or mind-body-spirit. Each card signifies different aspects of your question or situation. Interpret their meanings considering symbolism, intuition, and their positions in the spread. It offers holistic insights, illuminating past influences, present circumstances, and potential future outcomes, guiding your decisions and actions.</string>
    <string name="five_card_info">For a five-card draw, shuffle the deck and concentrate on your question. Draw five cards and arrange them in a spread, such as situation-challenges-advice-outcome-lesson. Each card represents a facet of your inquiry. Interpret their meanings, considering symbolism and intuition. This spread offers comprehensive insights, delving into the complexities of your situation, providing guidance for navigating challenges, making decisions, and learning from experiences.</string>
</resources>